A Guide to the Papers of Dr. Edward Watson Hook, Jr., 1947-1998
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- SERIES 4: Office Files, alphabetically arranged
  - Bone Marrow Transplantation May 1987-November 1989, 8 TLS, 2 TMemo, 1 TD, 1 TMs (Box-folder 015-009)
    Re: Development of bone marrow transplantation program at UVa; procedures.
  - Cancer Center April 1981-September 1990, 18 TLS, 5 TMemo, 2 TD, 1 TNS, 1 printed brochure (Box-folder 015-010)
    Re: Establishment, development of cancer center at UVa; personnel, space, funding issues.
  - Cancer Studies Division September 1970-March 198, 5 TL, 10 TLS, 1 TLS w/AN, 2 TD, 1 TMs (Box-folder 015-011)
    Re: Development of a comprehensive cancer program at UVa hospital.
  - Cardiology Division Correspondence September 1966-October 1987, 4 TMemo, 80 TLS, 5 TD, 1 ALS (Box-folder 016-001)
    Re: Personnel, staffing, patient care, funding, space allocation issues; procedures, history of division.
  - Cardiology, Correspondence (1982) January 1976-January 1983, 7 TL, 25 TLS, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 016-002)
    Re: Primarily contains 1982 correspondence with George A. Beller M.D., Head, Division of Cardiology but also includes Cardiovascular Research correspondence and information about the Hypertension Unit.
  - Cardiology, Correspondence (1983) January 1983-December 1983, 2 TLS w/AN, 14 TLS, 2 TD, 4 TL (Box-folder 016-003)
    Re: 1983 correspondence primarily with Head, Division of Cardiology, George A. Beller, M.D.
  - Cardiology, Correspondence (1984) March 1984-December 1984, 11 TLS (Box-folder 016-004)
    Re: Primarily the 1984 correspondence with George A. Beller M.D., Head, Division of Cardiology.
  - Cardiology, Correspondence (1985) January-December 1985, 4 TLS w/AN, 28 TLS, 2 TL, 1 AL, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 016-005)
    Re: Primarily the 1985 correspondence with George A. Beller, Head, Department of Cardiology, including funding, personnel, and space issues.
  - Cardiology, Correspondence (1986) January-December 1986, 72 TLS, 1 ANS, 1 TL, 3 TMemo, 1 AN, 1 TN (Box-folder 016-006)
    Re: 1986 correspondence primarily with George A. Beller, Head, Division of Cardiology and includes inpatient and outpatient fees, wellness center, computer systems, cardiac catheterization reports, and a discussion on the Adenosine Program project.
  - Cardiology, Correspondence (1987) January-December 1987, 50 TLS, 5 TD, 1 TL, 1 brochure, 1 AN, 1 TD w/AN, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 016-007)
    Re: 1987 correspondence, primarily with George A. Bellers, Head, Division of Cardiology and includes discussions on introducing new technology, LBJ Family Foundation, Cardiac Rehabilitation program, cardiac catheterization laboratory, animal research, and marketing strategy in the Cardiology Division.
  - Cardiology Division Correspondence February-December 1988, 2 TMemo, 47 TLS, 1 TD (Box-folder 016-008)
    Re: Personnel, staffing, patient care, funding space allocation issues; procedures.
  - Cardiology Correspondence January-May 1989, 52 TLS, 6 TMemo, 1 TD, 1 AMemo, 1 ANS (Box-folder 016-009)
    Re: personnel, staffing, patient care, space allocation issues; cardiology services for Martha Jefferson Hospital, finances.
  - Cardiology Division Correspondence June-December 1989, 43 TLS, 6 TMemo, 1 TD (Box-folder 017-001)
    Re: Personnel, finance, space allocation, staffing issues, cardiology services provided to Martha Jefferson Hospital.
  - Cardiology Division Correspondence January-November 1990, 42 TLS, 7 TMemo, 1 TD, 1 ANS (Box-folder 017-002)
    Re: Personnel, finance, patient services, space allocation issues; cardiology services offered by UVa to Martha Jefferson Hospital; same day catheterization; angioplasty; possible relationship with Augusta Hospital.
  - Cardiology-Camp Heart Teaching Center September 1984-August 1989, 12 TLS, 2 TMemo; 2 TD, 2 AN (Box-folder 017-003)
    Re: Establishment, use, scheduling of facility.
  - Cardiology Division - Cardiac Catheterization Lab 1971-1988, 15 TLS, 5 TD, 1 TMemo, 2 ANS (Box-folder 017-004)
    Re: Equipment malfunctions, increase in use and need for third lab, administration, patient scheduling.
  - Cardiology Division - Cardiac Rehabilitation January 1981-March 1982, 8 TLS, 1 TMemo, 3 TD, 1 AN, 1 TN (Box-folder 017-005)
    Re: Development of cardiac rehabilitation program at Boar's Head Sports Club.
  - Cardiology Division - Hypertensive Clinic 1968-1973, 8 TLS, 2 TMemo, 1 TD, 1 TMs (Box-folder 017-006)
    Re: Standards of care; funding; community program.
  - Cardiology Division - Coronary Care Unit April 1970-January 1989, 48 TLS, 10 TMemo, 3 TD, 5 AN (Box-folder 017-007)
    Re: Development of a mobile coronary care unit (establishment of guidelines); gift of Mrs. Lyndon Johnson to coronary care unit (July 2, 1973); renovations and equipment in CCU and admission and operational policies; CCU privileges; responsibilities of CCU residents.
  - Center for BioMedical Ethics October 1988-December 1989, 12 TLS, 4 TMemo, 3 TD (Box-folder 017-008)
    Re: Center's advisory board; also a draft of Biomedical Ethics at the University of Virginia which includes 4 goals: Biomedical Ethics in the Medical School Curriculum, Ethics Consultation Service, Advanced Education in Clinical Ethics, and Outreach Programs
  - Center for Prevention of Disease and Injury January 1984-December 1986, 21 TLS, 14 TMemo, 4 TD, 3 TMs, 2 ANS, 1 ALS (Box-folder 017-009)
    Re: Establishment of center; development of occupational medicine program, grant applications, personnel, contract with General Electric Co., Center Advisory committee meeting minutes.
  - Center for the Prevention of Disease and Injury February 1987-January 1989, 13 TLS, 22 TMemo, 2 TD, 1 TMs, 1 printed reprint, 1 printed newsletter (Box-folder 017-010)
    Re: Minutes of advisory committee, funding & grant applications, occupational medicine, affiliation with UVa departments & schools, residency program in preventive medicine, CPDI brochure, planning report.
  - Chairs March 1976-May 1990, 32 TLS, 3 TMemo, 2 printed brochures, 1 ANS, 3 TD (Box-folder 018-001)
    Re: Establishment, occupation of various Internal Medicine Chairs (Wood, Hunter, Janssen, Madge Jones, Nettie Marie Jones (Stone), Hook, and John Guerrant).
  - Chairs August 1973-October 1988, 38 TLS, 3 TMemo, 2 A memo, 2 TD, 2 TD, 1 printed brochure (Box-folder 018-002)
    Re: Establishment, occupation of various chairs (Jordain, Leavell, Mulholland, Peters, Richardson-Vicks, Scripps, Trolinger).
  - Chairs February 1961-March 1987, 33 TLS, 1 TMemo, 1 TD (Box-folder 018-00)
    Re: Establishment, occupation of Swineford chair.
  - China Trip December 1979-January 1981, 45 TLS, 3 ALS, 2 journal, 1 journal article, 1 printed card (Box-folder 018-004)
    Re: 1979 trip made by Hook as part of ACP delegation; subsequent visits by Chinese to University of Virginia, includes articles by Hook in Chinese.
  - Clerkships July 1982-July 1987, 22 TLS, 4 TMemo, 8 TD, 1 T/AD (Box-folder 018-005)
    Re: Evaluation of student & of physicians by students, content and structure of program, guidelines & procedures.
  - Clerkships January 1988-, 25 TLS, 4 TMemo, 3 TD (Box-folder 018-006)
    Re: Evaluation of students and of physicians by students, content, structure of program, personnel.
  - Clinical Pharmacology, Division June 1971-April 1990, 52 TLS, 7 TMemo, 3 TD, 1 ANS (Box-folder 018-007)
    Re: Funding & finances, grants, personnel, space & equipment, Poison Control Center.
  - Clinical Research Center October 1967-November 1987, 36 TLS, 7 TMemo, 5 TD (Box-folder 018-008)
    Re: Establishment of center, approval of research protocols, personnel, housestaff coverage, activities, location, grant funding.
  - Clerkships, Committee to Review November 1987-March 1988, 2 TMemo, 5 TLS, 3 TD (Box-folder 018-009)
    Re: Critique, evaluation, improvement of internal medicine clerkship.
  - Clinical Information Systems Executive Committee October 1988-April 1989, 6 TLS, 2 TMemo, 3 TD, 1 TNS (Box-folder 018-010)
    Re: Problems with new medical information system.
  - Clinical Laboratory Services Committee April-December 1989, [n.d.], 4 TLS, 2 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 018-011)
    Re: Medical Center laboratory activities.
  - Committee, Educational Policy Committee, School of Medicine October 1968-September 1970, 8 TL, 3 TLS, 2 Newpapers (Xeroxed), 3 TMemo, 11 TMemo w/AN, 8 TD, 4 TD w/AN, 2 TMS w/AN, 4 AN (Box-folder 019-001)
    Re: Covers Hook's involvement in the curriculum committee at UVa's school of medicine, includes Hook's handwritten notes on committee agendas.
  - Committees, Ethics May 1985-November 1988, 24 TLS, 4 TMemo, 7 TD (Box-folder 019-002)
    Re: Issues addressed by committee, minutes of meetings.
  - Committees, Ethics April 1990-May 1992, 18 TLS, 7 TMemo, 12 TD, 1 ALS (Box-folder 019-003)
    Re: Issues addressed by committee, meetings, minutes.
  - Committees, Ethics June 1992-January 1993, 11 TLS, 3 TMemo, 15 TD (Box-folder 019-004)
  - Committees, Ethics October 1983-December 1984, 28 TLS, 8 TMemo, 24 TD, 1 news article copy (Box-folder 019-005)
    Re: Development of Ethics Committee, issues addressed, minutes of meetings.
  - Committee on Extra Medical Center Activities October 1968-July 1986, 7 TD, 9 TMemo, 6 TLS, 7 TLS, 1 ANS (Box-folder 019-006)
    Re: Discussion of UVa's policy on house staff "moonlighting" at other organizations.
  - Committee, Finance October 1975-February 1976, 3 TMemo, 8 TLS, 9 TMS, 12 TD (Box-folder 019-007)
    Re: Items taken out of Hook's binder entitled, "Confidential: Finance Committee, Department of Medicine" - includes a report of the AdHoc Remunerations Committee, May 1975 and a Proposal for an incentive Plan of the Clinical Faculty of the University of Virginia School of Medicine.
  - Committee for Fundraising of the Department of Medicine December 1983-November 1986, 2 TLS, 10 TMemo, 12 TD, 1 TN, 3 TDS, 1 TMs (Box-folder 019-008)
    Re: Hook chaired a committee to oversee fundraising campaigns; established the Friends of the Department of Medicine.
  - Committees: Health Services Foundation Clinical Chairmen's Committee March-April 1990, 4 TLS, 2 news article copies (Box-folder 020-001)
    Re: Physicians participation in medicine, representation of Internal Medicine Department on the committee.
  - Committees: Health Services Foundation Executive Committee January 1982-July 1990, 10 TLS, 1 TNS, 1 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 020-002)
    Re: Requests for topics to be considered by committee, including malpractice premiums, control of expenditures, salaries, funding, radiology charges.
  - Committes: Human Investigation Committee May-October 1988, 12 TLS, 1 TMs, 1 TD (Box-folder 020-003)
    Re: Problems with research protocols.
  - Committees - Internal Medical Review Committee June 1981-October 1982, 14 TLS, 2 TMemo, 1 TD, 1 TMs (Box-folder 020-004)
    Re: Report of Dean Knorr's committee to renew department of internal medicine, and department member's response to report.
  - Committees: Internship/Residency 1970-1971, 14 TD, 14 TLS, 4 TMemo (Box-folder 020-005)
    Re: Number of positions per department, salaries, financing, new residencies, etc.
  - Committees: Internship/Residency 1972-1973, 12 TLS, 13 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 020-006)
    Re: Number of positions per department, salaries, new residencies, applications, financing, etc.
  - Committees: Internship/Residency 1974, 9 TLS, 7 TD, 2 TMemo (Box-folder 020-007)
    Re: Number of positions per department, salaries, new residencies, applications, etc.
  - Committees: Internship/ Residency 1975, 16 TLS, 10 TD, 2 TMemo (Box-folder 020-008)
    Re: Number of residents per department, primary care residents, applications, salary, budget, etc.
  - Committee: Internship Advisory Committee April-May 1989, 1 TMemo, 9 TLS (Box-folder 020-009)
    Re: Richard Guerrant chairs internship Advisory Committee.
  - Committees, Laboratory Quality Assurance May 1980-December 1982, 8 TLS, 2 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 020-010)
    Re: Response to JCAH criticism of floor labs at UVa.
  - Committees, Medical Center Development Committee January 1974-March 1976, 19 TLS, 1 TMemo, 19 TD (Box-folder 020-011)
    Re: Activities of committee to address space requirements, renovation, acute bed shortage.
  - Committee, Nursing December 1981-August 1986, 2 TLS, 2 TD (Box-folder 020-012)
    Re: Nursing shortage, pay differential
  - Committee, Professional Standards March 1988-July 1990, 23 TD, 3 TLS, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 020-013)
    Re: Minutes of comm. discussing various operational communication issues in Internal Medicine Department.
  - Committees, Quality Assurance April 1982-May 1990, 13 TLS, 3 TMemo, 5 TD, 1 ANS (Box-folder 020-014)
    Re: Meeting quality assurance, requirements of Joint Commission Accreditation.
  - Committees, School of Medicine Executive Comm. May 1975-November 1989, 26 TLS, 9 TD, 4 TMemo (Box-folder 020-015)
    Re: Admissions to school, naming of UVA hospital, faculty practice plan, items for agendas of meetings.
  - Committee, tenure November 9, 1984, 1 TLS (Box-folder 021-001)
    Re: Hook's position on tenure.
  - Transplantation June 1986-December 1988, 36 TLS, 11 TMemo, 10 TD, 1 ANS (Box-folder 021-002)
    Re: Establishment, structure, policies of transplantation program at UVa.
  - Committee, Medical Center Development June 1971-July 1973, [n.d.'s], 2 TMemo, 1 TLS, 1 TL, 4 TMs, 7 TD, 3 Photos (Box-folder 021-003)
    Re: Documentation of planning and development of UVa's hospital.
  - Confidentiality of Patient Records January 1984-January 1987, 3 TMemo, 4 TLS (Box-folder 021-004)
    Re: Incident involving breach of confidentiality & confidentiality policy.
  - Consultation March 1975-June 1986, 7 TLS, 3 TD, 2 TMemo (Box-folder 021-005)
    Re: Guidelines for consultations, problems with consultations.
  - Continuing Medical Education July 1985-February 1990, 2 TLS, 4 TMemo, 2 TD (Box-folder 021-006)
    Re: Continuing education events by Department of Medicine.
  - Council on Medical Education December 1972-February 1989, 23 TLS, 8 TMemo, 4 TD, 1 TMS, 1 T/AD (Box-folder 021-007)
    Re: Changes in curriculum, clerkships, teaching effectiveness.
  - Critical Care July 1981-April 1989, 28 TLS, 6 TMemo, 5 TD, 2 TMs (Box-folder 021-008)
    Re: Establishment of critical care, subspecialty at UVA, lack of critical care beds & establishment of a triage system.
  - CPR Training 1980-1986, 8 TMemo, 27 TLS, 6 TD, 1 ALS, 2 TNS, 2 AN (Box-folder 021-009)
    Re: Required CPR training and problems with payment/charges.
  - Diabetes Center April 1974-August1985, 11 TL, 2 TD, 1 TDS, 24 TLS, 4 TMemo, 2 receipts (Xeroxes) (Box-folder 021-010)
    Re: Diabetes Unit at Blue Ridge Hospital.
  - Diabetes Center (continued) January 1986-January 1989 & [n.d.'s], 28 TLS, 3 TMs, 3 TL, 7 TMemo, 2 TD, 1 TN (Box-folder 021-011)
  - DRG March 1985-July 1986, 3 TMemo, 13 TD, 10 TLS (Box-folder 021-012)
    Re: DRG reports for Department of Internal Medicine.
  - DNR January 1984-February 1990, 7 TLS, 1 TDS, 1 TD (Box-folder 021-013)
    Re: Do Not Resuscitate Policy
  - Emergency Medicine-Division of April 1973-August 1984, 20 TL, 26 TLS, 5 TD, 2 TMemo (Box-folder 022-001)
    Re: Concerns emergency room care while Hook was a professor of Internal Medicine and Chairman, Department of Medicine.
  - Emergency Medicine 1985-1988 January 1985-December 1988, 1 TL, 31 TLS, 1 TN, 2 TMemo, 2 TD (Box-folder 022-002)
    Re: Hook's involvement in ER administration including discussion on salaries, hiring faculty and faculties duties, triage policy, and security protection.
  - Emergency Medicine 1989-1990 January 1989-May 1990, 17 TLS, 4 TMemo, 6 TD, 1 AN (Box-folder 022-003)
    RE: Hook's involvement in ER administration including ER at Blue Ridge Hospital, development of health care facility at Lake Monticello, funding for 24 hour/7 day week faculty coverage, use of fellows as triage officers, GI bleeding, and budget concerns.
  - Employee Health Clinic January 1973-July 1983, 8 TL, 10 TLS, 4 TD (Box-folder 022-004)
    Re: Discussion includes the employee health clinic serving the entire medical center and themovement of clinic to new location.
  - Endrocrinology and Metabolism June 1972-December 1987, 13 TL, 2 TMemo, 33 TLS, 1 TD, 1 TDS, 1 AN (Box-folder 022-005)
    Re: Hook's involvement in the department of endrocrinology and metabolism including discussions on the tenuous relationship between endrocrinology and the department of pediatrics, budget and space concerns, the use of fellows instead of physicians to treat patients, and "competing" labs in endrocrinology.
  - Endrocinology and Metabolism (cont.) January 1988-June 1990, 22 TLS, 1 TL, 2 TD (Box-folder 022-006)
    Re: Hook's involvement with the Department of Endocrinolgy and Metabolism including discussions about purchasing equipment, space and budget concerns, and problems with the diabetes unit.
  - Epidemiology (1974-1990) September 1974-March 1990, 57 TLS, 6 TL, 1 Newspaper clipping, 4 TD, 2 TMemo, 3 ALS (Box-folder 022-007)
    Re: Hook's involvement with the Department of Epidemology, especiallyJack M. Gwalthey M.D., and includes discussion of HIV testing and ethics of testing blood of patients without patient identification.
  - Division of Family and Community Medicine May 1970-February 1987, 13 TLS, 2 TD, 2 TMemo, 1 TL (Box-folder 022-008)
    Re: Hook and William G. Thurman initially serve as co-chairmen of this division.
  - Fundraising January 1970-May 1988, 5 TL, 15 TLS, 1 TN, 4 TMemo, 1 TMemoS (Box-folder 022-009)
    Re: Hook's involvement of fundraising efforts for the Department of Internal Medicine including thank you's for gifts, possible financial contributors, and fundraising campaigns.
  - Funding - Rural Scholarship Program January 1971-July 1971 [n.d.], 3 TL, 6 TD, 2 TLS (Box-folder 022-010)
    Re: Giving scholarships to students from disadvantaged backgrounds, in particular rural areas.
  - Gamble, Elizabeth-Courtyard Garden April 1990-July 1994, 1 TN, 4 TL, 16 TLS, 2 TMemo, 1 AN, 1 Drawing, 1 AL, 1 Invitation, 1 TD (Box-folder 022-011)
    Re: Hook's involvement with dedicating a courtyard garden in honor of Elizabeth Brown Mulholland Gamble.
  - Gastroenterology, Division of Correspondence December 1978-June 1990, 75 TLS, 3 TL, 1 AN, 1 TLS w/AN (Box-folder 022-012)
    Hook's involvement with the Division of Gastroenterology, in particular department head, Richard McCallum.
  - General Faculty of the School of Medicine Meetings December 1972-November 1975, 4 TD, 1 TMemo w/AN (Box-folder 023-001)
    Re: Meetings that Hook was mentioned or directly involved with.
  - General Medicine July 1973-July 1982, 4 TMemo, 3 TD, 16 TLS, 19 TL, 1 AL, 1 TLSw/AN (Box-folder 023-002)
    Re: Primarily Hooks correspondence with Robert A. Reid, Primary Health Care, Ambulatory Division and includes handling and billing of ambulatory patients, primary care rotations, satellite clinic in Orange, and renovation of the primary care center.
  - General Medicine July 1983-April 1990, 31 TLS, 1 TL, 1 TMemo, 1 AN, 1 Newspaper clipping (Box-folder 023-003)
    Re: Issues and concerns concerning the Department of General Medicine headed by David Fedson, including patient cases & problems (one involving a racist patient), decline of patients in GMC, finances, GMC rotations and the activities of the primary care clinic.
  - General Medicine, Division of-Gordonsville Project July 1976-April 1981, 9 TLS, 1 TDS (Box-folder 023-004)
    Re: Non-profit medical center program in Gordonsville served by the Health Service Foundation.
  - General Medicine, Division of February 1982-June 1987, 24 TLS, 2 TL, 1 TD (Box-folder 023-005)
    Re: The medical center's branch in Orange.
  - Geographic Medicine, Correspondence September 1976-June 1990, 33 TLS, 8 TL, 3 TMemo, 1 AN, 1 TD, 1 TDS, 1 TMs, 1 Map (Box-folder 023-006)
    Re: Issues and concerns of the Deparment of Geographic Medicine headed by Richard Guerrant.
  - Geriatrics December 1977-December 1979, 9 TLS, 14 TL, 1 AD, 2 TMs (Box-folder 023-007)
    Re: Development of the Department of Geriatrics headed by Richard Lindsay; includes a 1977 proposed plan for UVa geriatric plan and testimony given before the joint subcommittee on Aging, The General Assembly, 1979.
  - Geriatrics January 1980-October 1981, 14 TL, 11 TD, 19 TLS, 2 TMemo, 1 TMemo w/AN, 1 Article (1st page), 1 AL, 1 TMs (Box-folder 023-008)
    Re: Development in the Division of Geriatrics, including proposals, reports, and house bills.
  - Geriatrics - Richard Lindsay March 1979-November 1981, 2 TMs, 2 TLS, 1 TL (Box-folder 023-009)
    Re: Development of programs for the elderly, including a 1979 manuscript, "A Survey of Geriatric Medical and Nursing Education in the United States and Virginia."
  - Geriatrics, Division of, Correspondence 1987 January-October 1987, 25 TLS, 1 TMemo, 1 TD w/AN, 1 Article, 1 TL, 1 TD (Box-folder 023-010)
    Re: Hook wants Geriatric medicine at UVA Hospital to be viewed as the first server for elderly and desires an interdisciplinary approach.
  - Geriatrics, Division of, Correspondence 1988 January-December 1988, 4 TL, 29 TLS, 3 TD, 2 TMemo (Box-folder 023-011)
    RE: Hook's involvement in promoting Geriatrics in 1988; requesting funds from the state for UVa's geriatric efforts, trying to get School of Nursing and School of Medicine to work together, geriatrics & Blue Ridge (Homeward Bound House), and accreditation.
  - Geriatrics, Division of, Correspondence 1989-1990 January 1989-May 1990, 43 TLS, 1 TD, 2 TMemo, 6 Maps (Box-folder 023-012)
    Re: Issues and concerns with the Division of Geriatrics including responsibilities of residents, plans for Nursing Home and Clinics, difficulties with the location of the Geriatric Clinics for the elderly patients, establishing the move of geriatrics Clinic to Blue Ridge, and assuming the space formerly occupied by the "Pink Ladies Canteen."
  - Geriatrics: ACGME Accreditation October 1986-March 1989, 8 TLS, 1 TMs, 7 TD, 1 AN (Box-folder 024-001)
    Re: Details Hook's involvement in attempting to secure accreditation for a training program in geriatrics and includes their grant application. After it was withheld by ACGME in 1988 and 1989, Hook challenges their decision.
  - Geriatrics, Division of Alzheimer's Disease, Nursing Home Research April-June 1985, 2 TL, 2 TN, 2 AN, 4 TLS, 2 TMemo, 2 TD, 1 TDw/AN (Box-folder 024-002)
    Re: Hook's involvement in discussing the possibility of a joint endeavor in the area of Alzheimer disease and long-term health care.
  - Geriatrics, Division of-Home Health Care January 1988-March 1990, 4 TMemo, 10 TLS, 1 TD (Box-folder 024-002)
    Re: Hook wants greater participation by the Department of Internal Medicine in the development of a home health care system.
  - Geriatrics, Division of Rehabilitation Unit July-September 1982, 1 TLS w/AN, 7 TMemo, 1 TD, 2 TLS, 1 TMs (Box-folder 024-040)
    Re: Documents include discussing the relationship between the School of Nursing and the Department of Geriatrics in establishing a Geriatrics/Rehabilitation Clinic at Blue Ridge Hospital. Includes in folder is a typed proposal and a typed manuscript, "Teaching/Research Nursing Home," written by Richard Lindsay.
  - Geriatrics, Division of-UVA Teaching Nursing Home October 1983-May 1987, 1 TLS w/AN, 2 TL, 2 TLS, 1 TD (Box-folder 024-005)
    Re: Hook desires faculty involvement in developing a teaching nursing home at UVA.
  - Geriatrics, Division of-Retirement Community-Marriot January 1987-January 1989, 10 TLS, 4 TMemo, 2 TMs (Box-folder 024-006)
    Re: Working out the contract agreement between UVA Health Services Foundation and the Marriott for the UVA retirement community, the Colonnades.
  - Geriatrics, Division of Shared Adult Home September 1984-September 1987, 3 TLS, 1 TN, 1 TMs, 1 TL (Box-folder 024-007)
    Re: UVa Hospital is interested in a Shared Adult Home with the City of Charlottesville and JABA.